HEY, GUYS, GUESS WHAT?
BARRY AND MINDY ARE
GETTING A DIVORCE.
( exclamations )
WHAT IS THE MATTER WITH YOU?!
NO-- BARRY AND MINDY.
OH. SORRY.
I HEAR DIVORCE, I
IMMEDIATELY GO TO ROSS.
WHO-WHO'S BARRY AND MINDY?
BARRY WAS THE GUY
THAT I ALMOST MARRIED
AND MINDY WAS MY BEST FRIEND.
WASN'T HE CHEATING
ON YOU WITH HER?
YEAH, BUT THAT JUST MEANS
THAT HE WAS FALLING ASLEEP
ON TOP OF HER INSTEAD OF ME.
AH.
GOD, COULD YOU IMAGINE
IF I'D ACTUALLY MARRIED HIM?
HOW DIFFERENT WOULD MY LIFE BE?
Ross:
I KNOW WHAT
YOU MEAN.
I'VE ALWAYS WONDERED
HOW DIFFERENT MY LIFE WOULD BE
IF I'D NEVER GOTTEN DIVORCED.
WHICH TIME?
THE FIRST TIME.
NO, SERIOUSLY,
IMAGINE IF CAROL
HADN'T REALIZED
SHE WAS A LESBIAN.
I CAN'T.
I KEEP SEEING IT THE GOOD WAY.
I BET I'D STILL BE DOING
MY KARA-TE.
TOWARDS THE END OF OUR MARRIAGE,
I WAS DOING A LOT OF KARATE
AS A WAY
OF RELEASING THE TENSION
FROM, YOU KNOW, NOT DOING
ANYTHING ELSE PHYSICAL.
MAYBE THE PROBLEM WAS
YOU WERE PRONOUNCING
IT "KARA-TE."
WHAT IF I WAS STILL FAT?
Y-YOU WOULDN'T BE DATING ME,
THAT'S FOR SURE.
SURE I WOULD.
OH, YEAH.
OH, COME ON.
WHAT? YOU GUYS
REALLY THINK I'M
THAT SHALLOW?
NO, I JUST THINK
MONICA WAS THAT FAT.
HEY, IMAGINE
IF I'D NEVER GOT FIRED
OFF DAYS OF OUR LIVES.
HEY, HEY, THERE'S CAROL AGAIN.
WHAT IF I HAD HAD THE
GUTS TO QUIT MY JOB?
I'D PROBABLY BE WRITING
FOR THE NEW YORKER--
BEING PAID TO BE FUNNY.
BUT MY JOB'S FUN, TOO.
I MEAN... TOMORROW, I...
I DON'T HAVE TO WEAR A TIE.
WHAT IF I HAD TAKEN THAT JOB
AT MERRILL LYNCH?
WHAT?
MERRILL LYNCH?
YEAH. I HAD A MASSAGE CLIENT
WHO WORKED THERE
AND HE SAID
I HAD A KNACK FOR STOCKS.
WHY DIDN'T YOU
TAKE THE JOB?
BECAUSE AT THAT TIME, YOU SEE
I THOUGHT THAT EVERYTHING
THAT RHYMED WAS TRUE.
SO, I THOUGHT, YOU KNOW,
IF I WORKED WITH STOCKS
I'D HAVE TO LIVE IN A BOX
AND ONLY EAT LOX
AND HAVE A PET FOX...
HEY, DO YOU GUYS THINK
IF ALL THOSE THINGS HAPPENED
WE'D STILL HANG OUT?
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN
YOUR DAY, YOUR WEEK ♪
♪ YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
OH, MY GOD.
RACHEL GREEN?
( gasping )
ROB TILLMAN.
NO...
( embarrassed chuckle )
NO, NO, IT'S ME, ROSS.
OH! I'M SORRY--
ROSS TILLMAN. OH!
NO. NO, NO.
ROSS GELLER.
OH, OF COURSE!
MONICA'S BROTHER!
YEAH, RIGHT.
WOW! HOW ARE YOU?!
GOOD. GOO...
I'M, I'M MARRIED.
OH. ME, TOO.
OH. WELL, OH...
ISN'T IT THE BEST?
OH, IT'S THE BEST.
( sighing simultaneously )
SO, UM, HOW'S MONICA?
OH, REALLY,
REALLY GREAT.
ACTUALLY, SHE'S RIGHT
DOWN THE STREET.
UM, DO YOU...?
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU SHOULD STOP
BY AND SAY HI.
OH, I WOULD LOVE TO.
OH, OH, SHE'D BE SO EXCITED.
OH, OKAY.
COME ON.
WAIT. DON'T YOU HAVE TO PAY
FOR YOUR... BUSTY LADIES?
NO, NO, NO, T-THAT'S OKAY.
SOME, SOME KID ASKED ME
TO PICK IT UP FOR HIM
( laughing ):
BUT I...
OH, OKAY.
SO, MONICA
STILL GOING OUT WITH
DR. BORING, HUH?
HE'S NOT BORING.
HE'S JUST...
HE'S JUST LOW KEY.
HERE WE GO.
ONE HAZELNUT LATTE.
THANK YOU.
YOU KNOW
THE HAZELNUT--
ACTUALLY NOT A NUT.
IT'S A SEED.
WOW.
CAN ANYONE ELSE
NAME A WELL-KNOWN SEED
THAT'S BEEN MASQUERADING
AS A NUT?
OH, DEAR GOD, LET ME THINK.
HEY.
Joey:
OH, NO. WHAT'S THE MATTER?
I JUST GOT
ANOTHER REJECTION LETTER.
THEY SAID MY WRITING WAS FUNNY,
JUST NOT "ARCHIE COMIC FUNNY."
YOU KNOW WHAT, HONEY?
I GOT TO GET BACK
TO THE HOSPITAL.
ALL RIGHT. MMM.
OKAY.
BYE.
OH, UH...
BY THE WAY, THE ANSWER IS...
THE BRAZIL NUT.
AH.
WAS HIS QUESTION
"WHAT'S MORE BORING THAN HIM?"
HEY, MAN, LOOK,
SORRY ABOUT THAT ARCHIE THING.
YOU NEED ME
TO GIVE YOU SOME MONEY?
HEY, I MAY HAVE NO MONEY,
BUT I STILL HAVE MY PRIDE.
REALLY?
EH...
HEY, MAYBE JOEY DOESN'T HAVE
TO GIVE YOU THE MONEY.
TV STARS HAVE ASSISTANTS,
RIGHT?
THAT'S AN IDEA.
HEY, IF I HIRED AN ASSISTANT,
WOULD YOU TAKE MONEY FROM HER?
NO, JOEY.
CHANDLER COULD BE
YOUR ASSISTANT.
SEE, HE COULD ANSWER
ALL YOUR FAN MAIL AND STUFF.
THAT WOULD BE GREAT.
LET'S DO THAT.
IT COULD GIVE ME TIME TO WRITE.
ALL RIGHT, GREAT.
WELCOME ABOARD.
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
I NEED TO USE THE BATHROOM
AND SINCE I DON'T NEED
ASSISTANCE IN THERE
TAKE A BREAK!
ALL RIGHT.
HEY.
Monica:
HEY, PHOEBE.
GUESS WHAT?
WHAT?
JOEY JUST HIRED CHANDLER
TO BE HIS ASSISTANT.
OH, THAT'S SO SWEET.
( phone ringing )
OH! HANG ON!
HANG ON!
( ringing continues )
GO.
NO. NO, NO.
I SAID SELL WHEN IT HITS 50.
FIVE-"O". IT'S A NUMBER.
IT COMES AFTER FOUR-NINE.
OH, IT'S OKAY. IT'S OKAY.
YOU'RE ALLOWED ONE MISTAKE.
JUST KIDDING.
YOU ARE, OF COURSE, FIRED.
OH...!
HEY, MON. MON.
LOOK WHO I RAN INTO.
( gasping )
OH, MY GOD! RACHEL!
GOSH, YOU LOOK TERRIFIC!
OH, SO DO YOU!
( laughing )
DID YOU LOSE WEIGHT?
YOU'RE SO SWEET TO NOTICE!
YES, I LOST
THREE-AND-A-HALF POUNDS!
AH!
( laughing )
AND, UH, YOU REMEMBER
MY FRIEND CHANDLER.
AND, UH,
AND THAT'S PHOEBE OVER THERE.
HI.
OH, MY GOD!
SIT DOWN.
HOW LONG HAS IT BEEN
SINCE WE'VE SEEN EACH OTHER?
1987--
THE DAY AFTER CHRISTMAS.
SHAUN McMAHAN'S PARTY.
I PLAYED YOU
ONE OF MY SONGS--
YOU KNOW, UH
"INTERPLANETARY
COURTSHIP RITUAL."
OH, YEAH.
RIGHT.
SO, UH, DO YOU
STILL DO MUSIC?
WELL, SOMETIMES.
YOU SHOULD COME OVER.
I'LL PLAY YOU
ONE OF MY...
OH, MY GOD!
JOEY TRIBBIANI
FROM DAYS OF OUR LIVES
JUST WALKED IN HERE.
RACH, HE'S A FRIEND OF OURS.
YOU ARE FRIENDS
WITH DR. DRAKE RAMORAY?
MM-HMM.
WELL, IT'S KIND OF HARD
TO BE FRIENDS WITH DRAKE
BECAUSE OF HIS BUSY SCHEDULE,
AND THE FACT THAT HE'S NOT REAL.
HEY, HEY, OR I COULD BRING
MY KEYBOARD HERE SOMETIME.
HE'S COMING OVER,
HE'S COMING OVER.
JOEY...
I KNOW. HERE, HERE.
OH...!
NO.
THIS IS MY FRIEND, RACHEL.
WE WENT TO HIGH SCHOOL
TOGETHER.
( hysterical laugh )
HI.
HI!
I LOVE YOU ON THAT SHOW!
OH...
I WATCH YOU
EVERY DAY.
I MEAN, WHEN YOU TOOK
OUT YOUR OWN KIDNEY
TO SAVE YOUR EX-WIFE
EVEN THOUGH SHE
TRIED TO KILL YOU...
WELL, IT'S ALWAYS NICE
TO MEET THE FANS.
AH...!
SHE'S NOT CRAZY, IS SHE?
NO, SHE'S COOL.
SO, UH...
HOW YOU DOING?
( hysterical giggles )
( phone ringing )
HANG ON.
GO.
WHO IS THIS?
OH, OKAY. YOU'RE GOING
TO LIKE WORKING FOR ME.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
WHAT KIND OF NAME IS BRINDY?
I... WHATEVE... STOP TALKING.
ALL RIGHT, FROM NOW ON,
YOUR NAME IS JOAN.
YOU CAN PICK YOUR OWN LAST NAME.
HEY, THERE YOU ARE.
UH-OH, IT'S MY BOSS.
ALL RIGHT,
HERE'S A LIST OF THINGS
FOR YOU TO DO TODAY.
MAN, THIS IS GOING
TO BE SO GREAT.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
I GOT TO GO TO WORK.
I'M DELIVERING TWINS TODAY,
BUT ONLY ONE OF THEM... IS MINE.
( snaps fingers )
( door shuts )
"DROP OFF MY DRY CLEANING,
PICK UP MY VITAMINS...
"TEACH ME
HOW TO SPELL VITAMINS...
WEAR IN MY NEW JEANS."
YOU REALIZE WHAT YOU ARE,
DON'T YOU?
WHAT?
YOU'RE HIS BITCH.
Phoebe:
NO! NO!
NO!
WAIT. YOU DIDN'T JUST SIT
ON MY KIT KATS, DID YOU?
NO. THERE WAS A LITTLE,
LITTLE DIP IN THE MARKET
AND I LOST $13 MILLION.
BUT THE KIT KATS
ARE ALL RIGHT?
WHAT AM I GOING TO DO?
WHAT AM I GOING TO DO?!
I CAN'T CALL MY OFFICE--
THEY'LL KILL ME.
I CAN'T CALL MY CLIENTS--
THEY'LL KILL THEMSELVES.
GREAT. NOW MY CHEST HURTS.
WHAT?
MY CHEST HURTS.
OH...
YEAH, AND NOW I,
I CAN'T BREATHE.
ARE YOU HAVING A HEART ATTACK?
IF I WERE, WOULD I
HAVE SHOOTING PAINS UP
AND DOWN MY LEFT ARM?
YES.
THEN, YES, THAT
IS WHAT I'M HAVING.
OH, MY GOD!
COME ON, PHEEBS, IT'S NOT
THAT BAD.
MOST PEOPLE
WOULD BE EXCITED
IF THEY DIDN'T
HAVE TO WORK FOR
A COUPLE OF WEEKS.
MOST PEOPLE
DON'T LIKE THEIR JOBS.
I LOVE MY JOB.
I'VE BEEN NOT WORKING
FOR THREE HOURS
AND I'M ALREADY GOING CRAZY.
I MISS JOAN.
HONEY, HAVING A HEART ATTACK
IS NATURE'S WAY OF TELLING YOU
TO SLOW IT DOWN.
I ALWAYS THOUGHT
HAVING A HEART ATTACK
WAS NATURE'S WAY
OF TELLING YOU TO DIE.
BUT YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO DIE.
I MEAN,
YOU ARE GOING TO DIE
BUT YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO DIE TODAY.
I WISH I WAS DEAD.
LET'S TAKE A WALK.
YOU KNOW, MAYBE YOU
SHOULD CONSIDER WRITING
FOR TALKING OUT OF
YOUR ASS MAGAZINE.
SO, WHAT'S GOING
ON WITH YOU?
WELL, UM, I'VE BEEN DOING
A LOT MORE OF MY KARA-TE.
STILL GOING THROUGH THAT
DRY SPELL WITH CAROL?
YEAH.
HOW LONG HAS IT BEEN
SINCE YOU'VE HAD SEX?
WELL... LAST WEEKEND...
OH, THAT'S NOT SO BAD.
...WILL BE TWO MONTHS...
SINCE I STOPPED TRYING.
MAYBE YOU NEED TO SPICE
THINGS UP A LITTLE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I DON'T KNOW.
YOU COULD TIE HER UP,
SHE COULD TIE YOU UP
YOU COULD EAT STUFF
OFF EACH OTHER.
HUH.
YOU KNOW, DIRTY TALK,
MENAGE A TROIS, TOYS...
WOW.
ROLE PLAYING.
YOU COULD BE THE WARDEN,
SHE COULD BE THE PRISONER
YOU COULD BE THE PIRATE,
SHE COULD BE THE WENCH...
OKAY, I THINK I GOT IT.
OR YOU COULD BE
TWO STOCKBROKERS
AND YOU'RE ROLLING AROUND
NAKED ON THE TRADING FLOOR,
AND EVERYBODY'S WATCHING.
IT NEVER HAPPENED.
ALL RIGHT, AND OVER THERE
IS BRADY'S PUB,
WHERE I LIKE TO UNWIND
AFTER A LONG DAY
OF SURGEONING.
WOW! OH, THIS
IS SO AMAZING.
WHAT ELSE? WHAT ELSE?
WELL, THAT IS A LARGE PIECE
OF TELEVISION EQUIPMENT
AND, UH, THAT IS AN OLD MAN.
HEY, OLD MAN.
HI.
ALL RIGHTY.
WHAT DO YOU SAY
WE HEAD BACK TO MY PLACE?
WELL, WELL...
UM, YOU KNOW, I WOULD
REALLY LOVE TO
BUT I-I SHOULDN'T.
WHY? WHY...
CAN'T THE WORLD STOP TURNING...
JUST FOR A MOMENT?
JUST FOR US?
ISN'T THAT A LINE
FROM THE SHOW?
UH... YEAH, BUT, UH...
I MAY HAVE SAID
THOSE THINGS BEFORE, BUT...
I NEVER TRULY MEANT THEM...
UNTIL NOW.
THAT'S A LINE FROM
THE SHOW, TOO.
OKAY, YOU WATCH TOO MUCH TV.
Chandler:
HERE YOU GO, JOE.
HE'S THE FRESHLY SQUEEZED
ORANGE JUICE YOU ASKED FOR.
THANKS.
YEAH, THERE'S PULP IN THAT.
YEAH.
( chuckles )
I THOUGHT
WE TALKED ABOUT THIS.
I DON'T LIKE PULP.
NO PULP.
PULP ISN'T JUICE.
ALL JUICE, OKAY?
I'M SORRY.
I GUESS I JUST... LIKE THE PULP.
OH, MY GOD, I'M SOR...
I AM BEING SO RUDE.
RACHEL, WOULD YOU LIKE A SODA,
OR SOMETHING?
BECAUSE... BECAUSE CHANDLER
WILL RUN RIGHT OUT
AND GET IT FOR YOU.
YEAH, WELL, SURE.
ICED TEA WOULD BE GREAT.
OKAY. ICED TEA.
OKAY. ANYTHING FOR YOU, SIR?
DID I NOT JUST TELL HIM
ABOUT THE...?
OKAY, LOOK, CHANDLER,
IF THIS... IS GOING TO WORK
YOU HAVE GOT TO LISTEN.
YOU'RE GOING TO THROW
THAT JUICE AT ME, AREN'T YOU?
IT'S NOT ALL JUICE.
SO, HONEY,
THIS MORNING WAS FUN, HUH--
ME HOPPING IN ON YOU
IN THE SHOWER THERE?
YEAH, AND MAYBE SOMEDAY
WE COULD GET A PLACE
WITH TWO BATHROOMS.
LOOK, CAROL, UM...
I WAS, I WAS THINKING,
MAYBE, UH
MAYBE WE CAN
SPICE THINGS UP A LITTLE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
CAROL, OUR SEX LIFE--
IT'S JUST NOT...
DAD!
HEY, THERE, LITTLE FELLA!
HEY, WHY DON'T WE GET
SOME SHOES ON YOU, HUH?
HEY, WHY DON'T YOU SHOW DAD
HOW YOU CAN PUT YOUR SHOES ON
IN YOUR ROOM? YAY!
YAY!
SERIOUSLY, OUR SEX LIFE...
I WAS THINKING MAYBE...
I DON'T KNOW,
WE COULD TRY SOME NEW THINGS
YOU KNOW, FOR FUN.
LIKE WHAT?
WELL, I DON'T KNOW. UM...
WELL, WHAT IF WE, UH, WERE TO...
TIE EACH OTHER UP?
( stifled chuckle )
UM, SOME PEOPLE...
EAT STUFF OFF ONE ANOTHER.
YEAH.
UM, YOU KNOW,
WE COULD TRY DIRTY TALK.
( forced chuckle )
UM, WE COULD,
WE COULD HAVE A THREESOME.
I LOVE THAT IDEA.
WHO SOLD A STORY TO
ARCHIE COMICS?
OH, MY GOD!
THAT'S SO GREAT!
OH, WOW!
YOU'RE A PUBLISHED WRITER!
I WISH I HAD A
PRESENT FOR YOU.
AW...
WAIT A MINUTE.
MY LAST KIT KAT BAR.
YOU WANT TO SHARE IT?
OKAY! OKAY.
HEY.
OKAY, CHANDLER,
LOOK
I KNOW YOU'RE MAD
BUT I JUST WANT TO SAY
I'M SORRY.
I WAS A TOTAL JERK.
COMPLETELY OVER THE LINE.
I JUST... I HATE PULP
YOU KNOW?
YOU KNOW HOW MONICA FEELS
ABOUT LOW-FAT MAYONNAISE?
IT'S NOT MAYONNAISE!
YEAH, OKAY, WELL, ANYWAY,
I JUST WANTED TO SAY I'M SORRY
AND HERE.
WHAT'S THIS?
FRESH SQUEEZED
ORANGE JUICE
WITH PULP,
JUST THE WAY YOU LIKE IT.
OH, THANKS, MAN.
HEY, JOEY, CHANDLER SOLD A STORY
TO ARCHIE COMICS.
OH, MY GOD, THAT'S GREAT!
CONGRATULATIONS!
WHAT'S THE STORY?
OH, YOU WOULDN'T, UH, CARE.
IT'S JUST A STUPID
COMIC BOOK STORY.
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
I LOVE ARCHIE,
AND THE WHOLE GANG!
WELL, UM, ARCHIE NEEDS
MONEY TO FIX HIS JALOPY.
( laughing )
UH, BUT HE DOESN'T
WANT REGGIE TO JUST
GIVE HIM THE MONEY...
SO REGGIE HIRES HIM
AS HIS ASSIS...
AS HIS BUTLER...
AND THEN MAKES HIM DO
ALL THESE CRAZY THINGS
LIKE BRING HIM MILKSHAKES
THAT CAN'T HAVE LUMPS IN THEM.
WAIT A MINUTE.
THAT SOUNDS A LITTLE FAMILIAR.
DID THEY ALREADY DO THAT ONE,
'CAUSE I THINK I READ IT.
OH, MONICA, LISTEN,
I HAVE TO ASK.
OKAY, JOEY TRIBBIANI INVITED
ME BACK TO HIS APARTMENT.
NOW, DOES HE DO THIS
WITH A LOT OF GIRLS?
YEAH, A LOT.
A LOT, A LOT.
OH, AND I'M ONE OF THEM!
WOW!
OH, I JUST CANNOT BELIEVE THIS!
I MEAN, JOEY TRIBBIANI!
YOU KNOW,
IT'S NONE OF MY BUSINESS
BUT AREN'T YOU MARRIED?
YEAH.
OH, I WISH
WE COULD JUST NOT BE MARRIED
FOR A LITTLE BIT.
YOU KNOW, I JUST WISH
WE COULD BE, LIKE, ON A BREAK.
WELL, YOU'RE NOT.
IT'S SO EASY FOR YOU.
YOU'RE NOT MARRIED.
YOU CAN HAVE SEX
WITH WHOEVER YOU WANT.
YEAH, I CAN.
AND DON'T THINK I DON'T,
BECAUSE I DO.
ALL THE TIME, YOU BETCHA.
MONICA?
HMM?
YOU'VE... YOU'VE
DONE IT, RIGHT?
( chuckling )
OF COURSE I HAVE.
WHAT DO YOU THINK, I'M, LIKE...
SOME 30-YEAR-OLD VIRGIN?
OH, MY GOD!
YOU'RE A 30-YEAR-
OLD VIRGIN!
SAY IT LOUDER.
I DON'T THINK THE GUY ALL
THE WAY IN THE BACK HEARD YOU.
Man:
YEAH, I HEARD IT.
IT'S NOT LIKE I HAVEN'T HAD
THE OPPORTUNITY.
I MEAN, YOU KNOW, JUST...
I'M JUST WAITING
FOR THE PERFECT GUY.
MM-HMM.
I'M SEEING THIS GUY, ROGER.
I MEAN,
HE'S NOT PERFECT, BUT, UH
I'M THINKING MAYBE
I SHOULD JUST GET IT OVER WITH.
YOU KNOW, GIVE HIM MY FLOWER.
OH, MY GOD, DO IT.
HONEY, YOU'VE
WAITED LONG ENOUGH.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU ARE RIGHT.
YES!
SEX DOES NOT HAVE
TO BE A BIG DEAL.
THERE SHOULDN'T BE
ALL THESE RULES AND
RESTRICTIONS, YOU KNOW?
PEOPLE SHOULD BE
ABLE TO SLEEP WITH
WHOEVER THEY WANT
WHENEVER...
RACHEL...
I'M NEVER GOING
TO THINK IT'S OKAY
FOR YOU TO CHEAT
ON YOUR HUSBAND.
OH, WHAT DO YOU
KNOW, VIRGIN?
PHOEBE?
WHY IS SMOKE
COMING OUT OF THE BATHROOM?
OH, YEAH, THE
DOCTOR SAID
THAT COULD BE ONE
OF THE SIDE EFFECTS.
PHOEBE, PUT THAT CIGARETTE OUT.
NO, IT'S NOT
A CIGARETTE.
THE SMOKE IS
COMING OUT OF ME.
PUT IT OUT!
OKAY, OKAY!
I'M SO GLAD YOU'RE HERE.
COME ON.
( phone ringing )
I GOT IT.
GIVE IT TO ME.
GIVE IT!
( karate yell )
HELLO.
NO, SHE CAN'T COME TO
THE PHONE RIGHT NOW.
OH. RIGHT.
NO PROBLEM.
OKAY, BYE-BYE.
WAS IT MY WORK? WERE THEY MAD?
WAS IT JACK? DID HE YELL?
JUST RELAX.
NOBODY YELLED.
JACK JUST WAS CALLING
TO MAKE SURE
YOU WERE GETTING BETTER.
THANK GOD.
YEAH, SHE'S FIRED.
You've done all you can,
Dr. Wesley.
You've got to let her go.
I suppose you're right, nurse.
Good-bye and Godspeed,
Hope Brady.
Not so fast, Wesley.
Ramoray.
That's right, Wesley.
I just stopped by to say that...
you're not a real doctor...
and that woman's brain...
is fine.
OH, THANK GOD!
OH, THANK GOD.
Hope.
Drake.
You're not dying,
Hope.
You're going to live
a long, healthy life...
with me.
Oh, Drake.
OKAY. HERE WE GO.
OKAY.
( clears throat )
MM...
HI, JOEY.
IT'S RACHEL.
UM, I AM FREE TOMORROW NIGHT.
YEAH, SURE. SURE,
I COULD BRING SOME SANDWICHES.
[Captioned by
The Caption Center
WGBH Educational Foundation]